Fares, please!
请买票!
Trafalgar Square, please.
请买一张到Trafalgar广场的票.
I'm sorry, sir. I can't change a ten-pound note.
对不起,我找不开10英镑的钞票.
Haven't you got any small change?
您没有零钱吗?
I've got no small change, I am afraid.
我恐怕我没有零钱.
I'll ask some of the passengers.
我来问问其他乘客.
Have you any small change, sir?
先生,您有零钱吗?
I'm sorry. I've got none.
对不起,我没有.
I haven't got any either.
我也没有.
Can you change this ten-pound note, madam?
夫人,您能把这10英镑的钞票换开吗?
I'm afraid I can't.
恐怕不能.
Neither can I.
我也不能.
I'm very sorry, sir.
非常抱歉,先生.
You must get off the bus.
您必须下车.
None of our passengers can change this note.
我们的乘客中没人能换开这张钞票.
They're all millionaires!
他们都是百万富翁!
Except us.
我们俩除外.
I've got some small change.
我有一些零钱.
So have I.
我也有.